Chase Harrington

Full Stack Developer

Well-qualified junior Full Stack Developer familiar with wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Handles any part of process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 6 months of related experience.

Work History

2020-11 - Handyman

Current

By His Hands LLC, Austin, TX

- Responded to maintenance requests in commercial and residential properties with great speed and efficiency.
- Prepared for new painting by removing previous materials with seam-cleaning, sandblasting, scraping and sanding.

2015-06 -2020-11

Team Lead

Mosquito Control Systems, Austin, TX

- Installed between 2-3 systems per day with approximately 3000 completed installations.
- Prepared detailed reports on updates to project specifications, progress, identified conflicts and team activities.
- Set up and calibrated machinery to meet specific production requirements and meet desired tolerances.
- Established open and professional relationships with team members which helped resolve issues and conflicts quickly.

2014-08 -

Call Center Representative

2015-05 IEnergizer, Austin, TX

- Helped customers who had issues in-game via email or phone calls.
- Helped test the game before release for bugs and other issues.

2013-07 -

Associate

2014-07

Walmart, Austin, TX

- Cashier
- Gun sales

2012-06 -2013-07

Sales Associate

Tractor Supply, Austin, TX

- Tracked stock using company inventory management software.
- Analyzed and properly processed product returns, assisting customers with finding alternative merchandise to meet needs.
- Organized racks and shelves to maintain store visual appeal, engage customers and promote specific merchandise.
- Maintained organized, presentable merchandise to drive continuous sales.
- Delivered high level of assistance by locating products and

Contact

Address

Austin, TX, 78758

Phone

(512) 961-9228

E-mail

acechaseharrington@gmail.com

Skills

Indoor and outdoor painting



Project Management



JavaScript programming



CSS proficiency



HTML expertise



Languages

Spanish

Japanese





checking store system for merchandise at other sites.

Education

2007-08 -	High School Diploma
2011-06	Leander High School - Leander, TX
2012-06 -	No Degree: General Studies
2013-01	Austin Community College - Austin, TX
2020-10 -	No Degree: Coding
Current	University Of Texas At Austin - Austin, TX